Guide to the Charles Gould Morris Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Charles Gould Morris family papers
1742-1961
MS 622
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
20
(48 boxes)
The papers consist of correspondence, writings, family papers, financial records, scrapbooks, daguerrotypes, and other material documenting the professional career of Charles Gould Morris and the personal lives of several family members. Morris's political career, his dairy business activities, and his municipal and civic concerns in Connecticut are documented. The letters and papers of family members involved in the settlement of the American frontier and in the Civil War are included, as are papers of Morris's father, Luzon Burritt Morris, a governor of Connecticut.
Morris, Charles Gould, 1871-1961
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Charles G. Morris, Elisabeth Woodbridge Morris, and the Charles G. Morris estate, mainly between 1940-1962. Gift of Mrs. Helen Forbes, 1991.
Arrangement
Arranged in three series and one addition: I. Personal Papers, 1825-1961. II. Family Papers, 1742-1960. III. Daguerreotypes and Photographs, 1850-1915.
Scope and Contents
The Charles Gould Morris Family Papers are composed of the personal, professional, and family papers of Charles Gould Morris and document his long career as a lawyer, businessman, public servant, and civic leader. The papers also contain materials relevant to Morris' ancestors, some of whom were long time residents of Newtown, Connecticut, to Morris' father Luzon Morris, a governor of Connecticut, and Morris' wife Elisabeth Woodbridge Morris. The papers are organized in three series: I. PERSONAL PAPERS, 1825-1961; II. FAMILY PAPERS, 1742-1960; III. DAGUERROTYPES AND PHOTOGRAPHS, 1850-1915.
Series I, PERSONAL PAPERS, contains most of the material in the papers from Morris' professional career and civic interests. Morris' legal activities are not well documented and are represented only by those estate files in which he had a personal interest (folders 117-125) and by financial records of the New Haven Organ Company, for which Morris served as successor trustee when the company was declared insolvent (folders 127-134). The papers more thoroughly illustrate Morris' business concerns. There are administrative and financial records of the New Haven Dairy Company, the General Ice Cream Corporation, and the Dolbey Ice Cream Company; records of dairy producers' associations; records of government agencies concerned with dairy regulations and arbitration; and Morris' speeches and writings relating to the dairy industry (folders 45-95). Some of these writings concern Morris' profit sharing system at Eastern Dairies. Morris' fiduciary responsibilities are represented only by a few records kept as president of the Broadway Bank and Trust Company (folders 3-4).
Morris' term in the Connecticut House of Representatives is not documented in the papers, but his three unsuccessful campaigns as Democratic candidate for governor (1924, 1926, 1928) are traced in correspondence, speeches, and scrapbooks of clippings (folders 160-171). Additional political speeches can be found in folder 181. During 1926 Morris also served on a governor's committee to investigate State Treasurer G. Harold Gilpatrick, who had misappropriated state funds. Folders 32-34 contain minutes of the committee meetings and correspondence with Governor Trumbull. For Morris' views on government see his manuscript A Citizen Thinks of His. Government(folder 182).
One of Charles Gould Morris' most enduring interests was civil service reform, both nationally and in Connecticut. Folders 5-31 all document various aspects of Morris' involvement through correspondence and printed material. Morris was also active in the affairs of Newtown, Connecticut. The papers contain records of town accounts and of the school board. The school board materials relate to routine concerns such as salaries, school calendar, and building repair, but also show the debate over the movement for school consolidation and the consequent need for bussing. Of note also are records of the nearby Fairfield State Hospital, of which Morris was a trustee. Folders 101-109 encompass committee records, board minutes, and correspondence for this mental health facility.
Through the Friends of Boys organization Morris became involved in the problems of delinquent boys, both in Hartford and New Haven. Records in folders 113-114 and 137-144 are composed of correspondence, reports, and memoranda. Included are daily memoranda written by John C. Collins, detailing his contacts with newsboys, bootblacks, and other New Haven street boys, the actions he took when problems arose, and the activities he organized for the boys' leisure time.
Among the other folders in Series I are photographs of Morris' comrades in the First Division Naval Battalion of the Connecticut National Guard (folder 39), materials from an 1898 survey of New Haven area religious institutions concerning their governance (folder 43), early naturalist. diaries in which Morris recorded his observations of birds and wildflowers (folder 99), and a scrapbook of early printed writings mainly by Morris' brother, Robert T. Morris (folder 183).
Series II and III relate to the family of Charles Gould Morris. Series II is composed of correspondence, scrapbooks, account books, writings, and other papers of Morris, Bennett, Tuttle, and Woodbridge relatives and others. Series III includes photographs and daguerrotypes of family members, residences, and friends. The papers include many family letters dating from the 19th century which were found in the old family home in Newtown. Folder 185 contains letters to Morris' grandmother, Lydia Bennett Morris, from relatives who moved west, to upstate New York, and folder 237 contains letters to her from a niece who had moved with her husband as missionaries to Wisconsin. Folders 238-239 contain letters from Martha Jane Morris, Lydia Bennett Morris' daughter, to her family describing her schooling, her teaching career, and, later, the growing family of brother Luzon Morris, near whom she lived.
Series II is rich in material from Charles Gould Morris' parents, Luzon Burritt and Eugenia Laura Tuttle Morris. For Luzon Morris there are legal files and account books from his law practice letters to his parents letters of congratulation on his election as governor, photographs of the gubernatorial staff, and memorial tributes following his death (folders 218-236). The series includes transcripts of Eugenia Morris' letters to her father Lucius Tuttle following her marriage in 1856. Other Tuttle family material includes copies of letters from Lucius Tuttle to family still in Connecticut describing his pioneering in Minnesota and a transcript of a diary kept by Eugenia's brother while aboard a Union blockade ship near Galveston during the Civil War (folder 249).
Eugenia Morris kept her other family records in scrapbooks. For each of her children she compiled a "Family Chronicle" in which she recorded her memories of their growth and development and in which she pasted photographs, children's letters, and drawings (folders 215-216). Her later scrapbooks (folders 256-257) include clippings about the gubernatorial election, memorabilia from the Cleveland inaugural and the Chicago Columbian Exposition, and pictures from European travels, as well as later material on her children and son-in-law Arthur T. Hadley. Her son, Morris' brother Robert, became a surgeon and naturalist. Eugenia Morris' scrapbooks contain copies of his writings, and folders 240-241 comprise the typescript for his memoirs Fifty Years a Surgeon.
In 1899 Charles Gould Morris married Elisabeth Woodbridge, a graduate of Vassar College and one of the first women to earn a Ph.D. from Yale University. Before her marriage Elisabeth Woodbridge had taught English and history at Vassar, and she continued to write and publish even as her family grew, The papers contain some of her writings, but the greatest quantity of material dates from her work with the Industrial Relations Club of New Haven and the Consumers' League. With other educated women, many of them wives of prominent Yale faculty, she organized studies and lobbying efforts concerning the working conditions in industries primarily employing women.
The series also includes records of the Morris children, primarily the youngest son Charles Lester Morris (folders 192-193), who was a student at Yale at the time this correspondence was written. Charles Gould Morris was interested in his family history and the history of the family home. Some of his correspondence and writings concerning these subjects can be found in folders 242-244.
The Charles Gould Morris Family Papers were donated to the Yale University Library between 1940 and 1962 by Charles Gould Morris, Elisabeth Woodbridge Morris, and the estate of Charles Gould Morris.
Biographical / Historical
Charles Gould Morris was born in Westville, Connecticut on February 4, 1871. He graduated from Yale College (B.A., 1895; LL.B., 1897) and owned and operated several ice cream and dairy businesses. Morris was active in New Haven municipal affairs and in civil service reform. He was an unsuccessful democratic candidate for governor (1924, 1926, 1928). He died in 1961.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Business; Child welfare; Civil service reform; Dairying; Education; Families; Ice cream industry; Industrial relations; Law; Milk; Public welfare; Women -- Employment; Connecticut -- Politics and government -- 1865-1950; Dairy plants -- Connecticut; New Haven (Conn.) -- History; Newtown (Conn.); United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Naval operations; Account books; Daguerreotypes; Diaries; Memoirs; Photoprints; Scrapbooks; Businessmen; Lawyers; Morris, Charles Gould, 1871-1961; Morris, Elisabeth Woodbridge, 1870-1964; Morris, Eugenia Laura Tuttle, 1833-; Morris, Luzon Burritt, 1827-1895; Morris, Robert T. (Robert Tuttle), 1857-1945; Connecticut. Board of Milk Control; Connecticut. National Guard. Naval Battalion; Dolby Ice Cream Company; Fairfield State Hospital (Newtown, Conn.); Friends of Boys (New Haven, Conn.); New England Dairy Corporation; New Haven Dairy Company; Vassar College; Yale University -- Students
- Personal Papers, 1825-1961; Series I; 15 linear feet (35 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains material arranged in alphabetical order by record type and/or topic.
  - Autograph and chirography collection, 1867-1915 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bills, receipts, bonds, 1895-1915 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Bank and Trust Company, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - Civil Service reform
    - Connecticut, State of. Advisory Personnel Committee
      - 1943-1947 (Box 2, Folder 5-7)
      - 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 8-10)
    - Connecticut, State of. Civil Service Commission
      - 1913 1915 January (Box 2, Folder 11-13)
      - 1915 February - 1921 (Box 3, Folder 14-18)
    - Connecticut Civil Service Reform Association, 1908-1923, undated (Box 4, Folder 19-23)
    - Connecticut Merit System Association, Inc.
      - 1936 - 1938 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - 1939 - 1945 (Box 5, Folder 25-27)
    - National Assembly of Civil Service Commissions, 1914-1916 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - National Civil Service Reform League, 1918-1920, 1930-1936 (Box 5, Folder 29-31)
  - Connecticut, State of. Governor's Committee in the Gilpatric Investigation, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 32-34)
  - Connecticut, State of. Jury Commission, 1935-1955, undated (Box 6, Folder 35-36)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1932-1960 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Connecticut National Guard: First Division Naval Battalion: correspondence and photographs re: service on U.S.S. Minnesota during the Spanish-American War, 1896-1938, undated (Box 7, Folder 38-39)
    General
    See also: box 34, folder 175-177
  - Connecticut Naval Reserve, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Connecticut State Guard, 1917-1919 (Box 7, Folder 41-42)
  - Correspondence: general, 1890-1960, undated (Box 7, Folder 43-44)
  - Dairy business
    - Dolbey Ice Cream Company, 1914-1925, undated (Box 8, Folder 45-48)
    - Eastern Dairies, Inc.
      - 1925 - 1926 (Box 8, Folder 49-50)
      - 1926 - 1935 (Box 9, Folder 51-57)
    - General Ice. Cream Corporation
      General note
      See: box 8, folders 49-57
    - International Association of Milk Dealers, 1921-1927, undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - National Ice Cream Manufacturers Association, 1913-1924, undated (Box 10, Folder 59-60)
    - New England Dairy and Food Council, 1922-1932 (Box 10, Folder 61-62)
    - New England Dairy Corporation
      - General, 1905-1907 (Box 10, Folder 63)
      - Minutes, 1899-1901 (Box 10, Folder 64)
      - Minutes, 1899-1906 (Box 11, Folder 65-66)
    - New Haven Dairy Company
      - General, 1901-1930, undated (Box 11, Folder 67-69)
      - Advertising, 1912-1915, undated (Box 12, Folder 70)
      - Annual reports, 1908-1930 (Box 12, Folder 71-72)
      - Statements, 1907-1925 (Box 12, Folder 73)
      - Treasurer's annual reports, 1907-1925 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Printed material, 1905-1922, undated (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Welfare and personnel, 1925-1927 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Writings, letters to editors, 1911-1927, undated (Box 13, Folder 77-78)
  - Dairy regulation and arbitration
    - General: Board of Arbitration of the New England Dairies, Inc.; Connecticut, State of. Board of Milk Control; Governor's Committee on Interstate Milk Relations
      - 1918 - 1932 June (Box 13, Folder 79-82)
      - 1932 July - 1935 May (Box 14, Folder 83-89)
      - 1935 June - 1947, undated (Box 15, Folder 90-93)
    - Speeches and writings, 1933-1937, undated (Box 15, Folder 94-95)
  - Daybook, 1867-1868, 1887-1890, n d. (Box 16, Folder 96-98)
  - Diaries, 1889-1898 (Box 16, Folder 99-100)
  - Fairfield State Hospital, 1929-1945, undated (Box 17, Folder 101-107)
  - Fairfield State Hospital, 1936-1944 (Box 18, Folder 108-109)
  - First Church of Christ (Center Church), New Haven, 1882-1888, 1905-1928, 1936-1938, undated (Box 18, Folder 110-112)
  - Friends of Boys
    See: box 18, folders 113-114 box 27, folder 137-144
  - Hartford Friends of Boys, 1930, 1936-1943, undated (Box 18, Folder 113-114)
  - Land records, 1893-1959 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Legal files
    - General, 1895-1924, undated (Box 19, Folder 116)
    - Estate records
      - Butterworth, George E., 1894-1903, undated (Box 19, Folder 117-118)
      - Hand, Daniel, 1891-1907 (Box 19, Folder 119)
      - Morris, Daniel, 1869-1932 (Box 19, Folder 120)
      - Olmstead, Harriet S., 1878-1919 (Box 19, Folder 121)
      - Peck, Janet Morris, 1858-1934 (Box 20, Folder 122)
      - Stone, Mrs. S.C., 1905-1907 (Box 20, Folder 123)
      - Stone, Sidney M., 1825-1900 (Box 20, Folder 124)
      - Tuttle, Laura A., 1848-1900 (Box 20, Folder 125)
    - McInerney v. Quinlivan, 1905-1907 (Box 20, Folder 126)
    - New Haven Melodeon Company
      See: box 20, folder 127
    - New Haven Organ Company
      - General, 1885-1913 (Box 20, Folder 127)
      - Daybooks
        - 1867 - 1871; 1879 - 1884 (Box 21, Folder 128-129)
        - 1876 - 1882 (Box 22, Folder 130)
      - Journal, 1872 (Box 23, Folder 131)
      - Ledgers
        - 1867 - 1873 (Box 24, Folder 132)
        - 1872 - 1881 (Box 25, Folder 133)
        - 1881 - 1884 (Box 26, Folder 134)
    - Sanderson v. Ives, 1909-1912 (Box 27, Folder 135)
  - Military Order of the Serpent: Grand Lair of Connecticut, 1910 (Box 27, Folder 136)
  - New Haven Friends of Boys
    - Correspondence, reports, 1925-1927, undated (Box 27, Folder 137)
    - Memoranda
      - 1925 August - 1929 August (Box 27, Folder 138-140)
      - 1927 September - 1931 Feb, 1932 March - April (Box 28, Folder 141-144)
  - New Haven Taxpayers, Inc., 1935-1940, undated (Box 28, Folder 145)
  - Newtown, Connecticut
    - General, 1920, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 146)
    - Committee to Investigate the Records of the Probate District, undated (Box 28, Folder 147)
    - School Board, 1922-1943 (Box 29, Folder 148-150)
    - Town accounts, and investigation, 1894-1909 (Box 29, Folder 151-153)
    - Town accounts, and investigation, 1894-1909 (Box 30, Folder 154-155)
    - Zoning act, 1953-1954 (Box 30, Folder 156)
  - Personal papers and memorabilia, 1901-1944, undated (Box 30, Folder 157)
  - Politics
    - Democratic Party, 1923-1936, undated (Box 30, Folder 158)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1942-1943 (Box 30, Folder 159)
    - Gubernatorial campaigns:
      - 1924 (Box 30, Folder 160-161)
      - 1924 (Box 31, Folder 162-165)
      - 1926 (Box 31, Folder 166)
      - 1928 (Box 32, Folder 167-168)
      - 1928 (Box 33, Folder 169)
      - undated (Box 34, Folder 170-171)
    - Legislation, 1919-1959, undated (Box 34, Folder 172)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1929-1931, 1944, undated (Box 34, Folder 173)
  - Printed material, 1916-1953, undated (Box 34, Folder 174)
  - Spanish-American War
    See: box 7, folders 38-39 box 34, folder 175-180
  - United Spanish War Veterans
    - General
      - 1917 - 1923 (Box 34, Folder 175-177)
      - 1924 - 1944, 1958, undated (Box 35, Folder 178-179)
    - Pershing Fourth of July Fund, 1918-1920 (Box 35, Folder 180)
  - Writings
    - Articles, speeches, letters to editors, 1894-1961, undated (Box 35, Folder 181)
      See also: box 7, folder 40 box 13, folder 77-78 box 15, folder 94-98 box 30, folder 160-171 box 42, folder 237 box 44, folder 242-244
    - A Citizen Thinks of His Government, 1904-1948 (Box 35, Folder 182)
    - Scrapbook of articles by Morris family members, 1887-1907, undated (Box 35, Folder 183)
  - Yale University, 1886, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 184)
- Family Papers, 1742-1960; Series II; 6.0 linear feet (12 boxes)
  This series is arranged in alphabetical order by name of family member. Oversize materials are grouped together at the end.
  - Beardslee, Aaron (Box 36, Folder 184a)
    See: box 45, folder 253
  - Bennett family: letters and transcripts, 1835-1875, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 185)
  - Clark, W.S.: ledger, 1866-1868 (Box 36, Folder 186)
  - [Clark, W.S.?]: ledger, 1866-1867 (Box 36, Folder 187)
  - Cressler, Alfred D.: coal storage, 1918-1926 (Box 36, Folder 188)
  - Glasso, Joseph: sheet music, undated (Box 36, Folder 189)
  - Jackson, Elisabeth Woodbridge (Morris): diary, 1928-1929 (Box 37, Folder 190)
  - Moore family: letters, 1843; 1848 (Box 37, Folder 191)
  - Morris, Charles Lester: letters and miscellanea, 1928-1930, undated (Box 37, Folder 192-193)
  - Morris, Daniel
    See: box 19, folder 120
  - Morris, Eli Gould
    See: box 45, folder 254
  - Morris, Eli James: letters, 1860-1891, undated (Box 37, Folder 194)
  - Morris, Elisabeth Woodbridge
    - Camp Arden, 1924, undated (Box 37, Folder 195)
    - China: letters and leaflets, 1930-1941, undated (Box 37, Folder 196)
    - Connecticut State Council of Defense: Woman's Committee, 1918 (Box 37, Folder 197)
    - Hadley, Hamilton: typescript, "Why Every Woman Should Vote for Smith", 1928 (Box 37, Folder 198)
    - Hopkins Grammar School: 275th anniversary historical pageant, 1935 (Box 37, Folder 199)
    - Labor relations
      - American Youth Congress, 1935, undated (Box 37, Folder 200)
      - Beauty shops, 1934-1935, undated (Box 37, Folder 201)
      - Child Labor Amendment, 1934-1935, undated (Box 37, Folder 202)
      - Domestic workers, 1935, undated (Box 37, Folder 203)
      - Industrial Relations Club of New Haven, Consumers' League of Connecticut (Box 38, Folder 204-207)
        See also: box 45, folder 255
      - Legislation, 1935, undated (Box 38, Folder 208)
      - Printed material, 1933-1934 (Box 38, Folder 209)
      - Women in industry, 1933-1934, undated (Box 38, Folder 210)
    - Personal correspondence and memorabilia, 1925-1960, undated (Box 38, Folder 211)
    - Vassar college: 50th anniversary speech and memorabilia, 1915 (Box 38, Folder 212)
  - Morris, Eugenia Laura Tuttle
    - Commonplace book, 1886-1925, undated (Box 39, Folder 213)
    - Correspondence and transcripts, 1869-1888, 1916, undated (Box 39, Folder 214)
    - Journals and scrapbooks: "Family Chronicles", 1873-1889, 1913 (Box 39, Folder 215-216)
      See also: box 46, folders 256-257
  - Morris, James and others: daybook, 1808-1829 (Box 39, Folder 217)
  - Morris, Luzon Burritt
    - Album: photographs of government staff, undated (Box 40, Folder 218)
    - Sean, James, The Christian Minister's Affectionate Advice to a Married Couple, 1856 (Box 40, Folder 219)
    - Certificates of appointment as notary public, 1884-1895 (Box 40, Folder 220)
    - Correspondence and transcripts, 1832-1894, undated (Box 40, Folder 221)
    - Daybook, 1856-1874 (Box 40, Folder 222)
    - Ledgers, 1856-1867 (Box 41, Folder 223-225)
    - Legal files
      - General: letterpress copybook, 1856-1874 (Box 41, Folder 226)
      - Estate records
        - Higgins, Sarah, 1875-1883 (Box 41, Folder 227)
        - Peck, Sylvester, and Fanny Peck, 1855-1870, undated (Box 41, Folder 228)
        - Whitney, Eli: general, and trust for Chaplain family, 1872-1895, undated (Box 42, Folder 229-230)
      - Platt v. Platt, 1874-1875 (Box 42, Folder 231)
      - Quinnipiac Bridge, Fair Haven, Connecticut, 1874 (Box 42, Folder 232)
      - Miscellaneous financial records, land records, etc., 1818-1895, undated (Box 42, Folder 233)
    - Letters of congratulation, 1892 (Box 42, Folder 234)
    - Memorial tributes, [1895] (Box 43, Folder 235)
    - Record book: legal cases, committee hearings, 1884-1892 (Box 43, Folder 236)
      See also: box 46, folder 256
  - Morris, Lydia Bennett: letters and transcripts, 1842-1874, 1938-1945, undated (Box 43, Folder 237)
  - Morris, Martha Jane: letters and transcripts, 1850-1877, 1934, undated (Box 43, Folder 238-239)
  - Morris, Ray
    See: box 35, folder 183
  - Morris, Robert Tuttle: Typescript, Fifty Years a Surgeon, Circa1934 (Box 43, Folder 240-241)
    See also: box 35, folder 183
  - Morris family
    - Notes and writings, 1908-1948, undated (Box 44, Folder 242-243)
    - Historical papers, 1742-1911, undated (Box 44, Folder 244)
    - Memorabilia, undated (Box 44, Folder 245)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and papers, 1869-1945, undated (Box 44, Folder 246)
  - Parsons, Klapp, Brinckerhoff -- Douglas: report, 1929 (Box 44, Folder 247)
  - Thompson, James W.: account book, 1878-1894 (Box 44, Folder 248)
  - Tuttle, Laura A.
    See: box 20, folder 125
  - Tuttle, Lucius Bement: Civil War diary and letters (transcripts only), 1856-1874; 1924 (Box 44, Folder 249)
  - Woodbridge, A.D.: letters and poem, 1841-1854 (Box 44, Folder 250)
  - Woodbridge, Charles L.: passport, 1873-1883 (Box 44, Folder 251)
  - Unidentified: recipe book, undated (Box 44, Folder 252)
  - Oversize
    - Beardslee, Aaron: farm ledger, 1790-1823 (Box 45, Folder 253)
    - Morris, Eli Gould: form ledger, 1822-1861 (Box 45, Folder 254)
    - Morris, Elisabeth (Woodbridge): scrapbook, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 255)
    - Morris, Eugenia Laura (Tuttle): scrapbook
      - 1891 - 1895 (Box 46, Folder 256)
      - 1896 - 1905 (Box 47, Folder 257)
- Daguerrotypes and Photographs, 1850-1915; Series III; 0.5; (1 box)
  This series is arranged in two sections, Daguerreotypes and Photographs. Each section is arranged in alphabetical order.
  - Daguerreotypes
    - Baker, Origen: "ae 16-17. Brooklyn. A Wilton boy.", undated (Box 48, Folder 258)
    - Baldwin, Emily, undated (Box 48, Folder 258)
    - [Baldwin, Emily?], undated (Box 48, Folder 259)
    - Bull, Willie: "about 1861", Circa1861 (Box 48, Folder 259)
    - Cochrane, John: "one of father's clerks (Seymour)", undated (Box 48, Folder 259)
    - Demarest, Miss S.M.: "where Emily -- I taught", undated (Box 48, Folder 260)
    - Harrison, Viola: "Brooklyn", undated (Box 48, Folder 260)
    - Higgins, "Aunt" Sarah, undated (Box 48, Folder 260)